

# Ahmed Škulj

Software Egineer / Junior Frontend Developer

### **Details**

#### Address:

Ulica Patriotske Lige 94 Kakanj, 72240 Bosnia and Herzegovina

#### Phone:

061/957/535

#### Email:

ahmedskulj10@gmail.com

#### Github:

https://github.com/ahmedskulj00/

## Skills

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

React

SQL

Node.js

C++

**Typescript** 

## Languages

**Bosnian** 

**English** 

## About me

A Software Engineer from Bosnia and Herzegovina. I have graduated from University of Zenica, with a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering. Love to work with front-end technologies . I have already worked as a Junior Software Developer so I have experience in the industry. I'm a hardworking person and I think that only hard work and consistency are keys to success.

# **Employment History**

Frontend Developer, Viberate

May 2022 - July 2022 PRemote

- Worked on Viberate app.
- Learned a lot about charts implementation in React
- Learned about PDF exporting in React

Junior Frontend Developer, Purple Key

Dec 2021 - May 2022 **♀** Sarajevo

- Worked on different projects using React.
- Learned about different tips and tricks for better development
- Worked on my UX/UI skills

Junior Software Developer, Mistral Technologies

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021 Sarajevo

- Worked with mentor on different tasks in React.
- Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Learned about agile development

## Education

Grammar School "Muhsin Rizvić", Kakanj

Software Engineering, University of Zenica

# Relevant Projects

Portfolio - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Quiz App - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

Weather App - HTML, CSS, JavaScript